[The Heir]
[Episode 36]
Ronghua,
you've finally come around.
Although you won't be the legitimate wife,
the dowry we prepared for you
lacks nothing.
When you take these with you
into your new household,
people will envy you.
You are right, Mother.
I was ignorant before
and lost my temper.
Today, I just want
to take a good look
at the dowry with you,
so as not to waste all the care
you and Benchang put into this.
Let's go. Let me show you.
Come in, Ronghua.
Look at these.
These are all your dowries.
Silks and satins.
Wedding quilts.
And here is...
jewelries.
Everything you need.
Nanjing is far away from home.
So your father, brothers, and I
cannot take care of you all the time.
So all we can do is make sure
your dowry wants for nothing.
We won't let you suffer a single slight
in your husband's house.
Mother,
you've been most thoughtful,
arranging all these fine things for me.
But as the saying goes,
old clothes are better.
Can I take all my old clothes
with me?
Those are all old clothes.
Why do you want to take them?
Because many of them
were made by you.
I want to keep them
to keep a piece of home with me.
Thank you, Ronghua,
for keeping me in your heart.
Okay.
I'll go prepare them for you.
You can take another look.
Mother.
Where did you go?
Well,
Ronghua came around
and wanted to see the dowry.
So I took her
to the warehouse to have a look.
She was quite satisfied.
Well,
I'll go help her pack some other things.
Benchang, why are you here?
Nothing.
Mother said you were here
looking over the dowry,
so I came by to take a look.
If there is anything missing,
I can get it for you in time.
Nothing is missing.
After all,
I belong to the Tian family.
I will do the thing I ought
to do for the Tian family.
After trying on many clothes,
I'm tired.
I want to go to the tearoom for a rest.
My Lady, Madam said
you should go back after trying them on.
Enough.
Do I need your permission
to have a cup of tea?
Just wait here,
and don't follow me.
Zhen.
You were right.
The contraband ink
was hidden in the dowry.
Did you see it clearly?
How much is there?
If there are dozens of sticks in each box,
that would be
over a thousand sticks in total.
Over a thousand sticks?
This is a capital offense.
Tian Benchang wants
to be an official so badly
that he is willing to risk his life.
Zhen.
At this point,
I have nothing to be afraid of.
Why don't we go straight
to the prefectural office
and report this to Prefect He?
No.
The prefectural office
is full of Tian Benchang's spies.
If we report it rashly,
before we even see Prefect He,
Tian Benchang will get the news
and move the contraband ink.
If we want to catch him,
we must catch him red-handed.
But he's always cautious.
How can we hide it from him?
Ronghua.
When you get married tomorrow,
Tian Benchang will definitely escort you
out of the city, right?
Of course.
You and I have similar figures.
I will take your place
in the bridal sedan chair tomorrow.
Zhen, it's too dangerous.
I can't let you take this risk.
Ronghua, I'm not only doing this for you,
but also for myself and the Li family.
Tomorrow,
when the bridal sedan
arrives at Sibao Street,
I will stop it.
Xiao Qi and Doggie will help me
lay the contraband ink
hidden in the dowry
before everyone.
When we catch him red-handed,
no matter how cunning Tian Benchang is,
he won't be able to deny it.
As for your marriage,
it will naturally be invalid
since it involves Tian Benchang's
illicit foreign trade and bribery.
Ronghua, this time,
you must listen to me.
Ronghua, let's go separately.
I will take the back door.
Go home quickly,
so as not to arouse suspicion.
Go quickly.
Ungrateful traitor!
Benchang.
Since it has come to this,
are we still going
to move the ink tomorrow?
Nonsense.
If the ink doesn't
leave the city tomorrow,
we'll miss the river shipment.
If we delay the delivery,
we won't be able to get the money back.
Since Li Zhen wants to stage
a bride-swap trap
to catch me red-handed.
Well.
I'll let her know
what it means to be too clever
and dig her own grave.
[Changsheng Garden]
You guys go over there. Come on.
This way. This way.
What time is it?
It is already past the Hour of Chen.
Go check on my parents and Benchang
and see if they are ready.
Yes.
Ronghua.
It's me.
Zhen, I was worried about you.
I was wondering
why you hadn't come yet.
Ronghua, don't worry.
We'll proceed as planned.
Don't worry.
Keep a close watch on this courtyard.
Don't let anyone in or out.
Zhen, go hide.
Hide behind the screen. Go quickly.
Okay.
Benchang, why are you here?
Search.
How dare you!
Tian Benchang, what are you doing?
Let me go!
Let go!
-Zhen!
-Ronghua!
Let her go! Let her go!
-Zhen.
-Let go!
You and Ronghua's friendship
is moving indeed.
What a pity.
You miscalculated.
You're no match for me after all.
Tian Benchang, I know all
about your trading your own sister
for power and profiting
from illicit foreign trade.
Don't make any more mistakes.
Drag her out.
Get her in the bridal sedan chair.
Don't touch me!
Ronghua!
Zhen.
Zhen!
Ronghua!
Let me go!
Let me go! Zhen!
Let me go! Let me go!
Let me go!
Tian Benchang!
You're trading your own sister
for glory and riches.
You are shameless!
Zhen.
Once I've sent Ronghua
into the bridal sedan chair,
I'll come back and deal with you.
Tie her up.
Yes!
Let me go!
Let go!
Ronghua!
If you really care about Zhen's safety,
just behave and get married.
Otherwise,
you'll be the one to drive her to ruin.
Keep a close watch on Ronghua.
Yes.
Has everything been arranged
with Officer Zhang?
It's all taken care of.
Benchang, don't worry.
I will make sure Ronghua
leaves the city safely.
Go out and guard the courtyard.
Without my order,
don't let anyone in.
Yes.
Tian Benchang.
You illegally imprison a civilian.
Aren't you afraid someone
will report you to the prefectural office
and bring troops to arrest you?
You trespassed into the Tian Residence
and disturbed my sister's wedding,
causing a public disturbance.
Even if we go to court in the future,
I am the one in the right.
Besides,
aren't your accomplices
all on Sibao Street right now,
waiting to stop the bridal sedan chair?
Who will care about you?
What did you say?
Li Zhen.
Let me tell you the truth.
Today on Sibao Street,
not only will they not find anything,
but they will also end up bearing
the charge of disrupting a wedding
and be taken back
to the prefectural office for punishment.
If you want to outsmart me,
you still have a long way to go.
Tian Benchang,
you're shameless!
Don't touch me.
Zhen.
Today is really a good day.
Ronghua is getting married,
and it also happens to be the last day
of your Li family's half-month deadline.
After today,
the Li family's charge
of illicit foreign trade
will be fully confirmed,
and there will be no turning back.
Zhen.
When did your eyes
become so fierce and ruthless?
I remember the way
you used to look at me,
your eyes always
curved like a crescent moon.
It was adorable.
Let me take a closer look at you.
Tian Benchang!
Don't touch me, Tian Benchang!
Let me go!
Sit down!
Zhen.
Before we were supposed to get married,
you always acted spoiled with me
and asked me
to draw your eyebrows in the future.
How about I draw them for you today?
Come here.
Li Zhen.
I know you hate me.
But what did I do wrong?
I was born poor
and burdened by my family's situation.
So I had no choice but to risk everything
for a better future.
Before,
you were a part of my future.
It's a pity you didn't understand.
Not only did you not understand,
but you also crushed my heart
and got involved with Luo Wenqian.
Li Zhen.
From the moment you stepped
out of that sedan chair
to break off the engagement,
you chose the wrong path
and the wrong person.
Today,
you are at my mercy.
Tian Benchang.
You've always gone against
and compared yourself to Wenqian.
In the end,
you just feel inferior deep down.
You are jealous of his talent,
his background,
and his character.
And what's more, you're jealous
that I love him but hate you.
Even if he is a prisoner now,
in my heart,
he is a hundred or a thousand times
more important than you!
Say that again!
You always say you were burdened
and forced by your background.
But back then, when our whole family
squeezed into a small place
in City Gate Lane,
compared to your family,
the situation was even harder.
And Wenqian—
his family was ruined.
How was he any better off than you?
But over the years,
we've never been like you,
doing whatever it takes
to achieve our goals.
In truth,
you are nothing but a hypocrite,
selfish to the core.
You
don't deserve me.
I don't deserve you?
I secured the tribute ink contract
for the Tian family.
And  I am the manager of Tian Ink.
Once I get a position
in the Directorate of Imperial Household,
not to mention the Hui Ink families,
even Lord Yan and Prefect He
will have to show me respect.
Do you think you can keep the position
after trading your sister for it?
Tian Benchang,
the higher you climb, the harder you fall.
Whether I can keep it is my own ability.
It's none of your concern.
You'd better worry about yourself first.
How about this?
I'll give you one last chance.
As long as you promise me
to be obedient from now on,
I'll let
what happened today slide.
I can even find a scapegoat
to take the blame
for the Li family's illicit foreign trade.
Then you can be with me again.
How about it?
Dream on.
Stop there.
Don't come any closer.
Don't come any closer!
Right.
Just like that.
Over the past few years,
every waking moment, I imagined
making you wholly mine
and bringing you completely to heel.
Tian Benchang.
Kill me
if you dare!
Having the Tian family bear another life
will make my trip worthwhile.
What?
You don't dare?
Lost your nerve?
Benchang.
Benchang!
-Tian Benchang!
-Benchang!
Calm down. Calm down.
Benchang.
Speak.
Everything went as you expected.
Ronghua's wedding sedan
was stopped as soon
as it arrived at Sibao Street.
Those rebels
have been taken to the prefectural office
by Officer Zhang to be punished.
Bensheng.
You handled this matter
quite well.
Has Ronghua's sedan left the city?
In an hour,
they will meet up
with the welcoming procession.
Li Zhen,
you heard all that?
Your accomplices have all been taken away
by the authorities.
Ronghua has also left the city.
In the end,
you can't do anything.
Benchang,
the obstacles have been cleared.
Shouldn't we get down to business?
Have someone watch her.
Bring her some food and drinks.
Before we come back,
make sure she stays alive.
Benchang, if you are not feeling well,
I can deliver those things myself.
Idiot.
What's the use of you going?
Now everyone is on edge.
If I don't show up in person,
how would they dare to accept the goods?
Let's go.
Eldest Young Master,
all goods have been accounted for.
According to the original plan,
you guys move the ink
out of the city first.
We will follow behind.
Let's meet up outside the city.
Yes.
Benchang,
isn't that Chen Junshan?
If the Chen family
sees this batch of ink,
we are doomed.
Baixi Village—
It's the closest place to us.
The village is full of our people.
As long as we get in, we'll be safe.
Go to Baixi Village!
Tian Benchang
is heading towards Baixi Village.
Hurry and inform those of Huang Ink
to block them on their way.
Yes!
Benchang, what do we do now?
What are you panicking about?
What a bunch of mob!
My Tian family is an imperial merchant,
the leading ink house
in Huizhou ink industry.
You openly block us here.
Are you forcing me to sue
at the prefectural office
and have you all punished?
What "leading ink house"
are you talking about?
Tian Ink has repeatedly
disrupted the order of the ink industry.
Tian Benchang,
your good days are over today!
Manager Huang,
why bother talking to him?
Search the ink directly!
I'd like to see who dares!
Prefect He has arrived.
Thank you.
Zhen.
Ronghua.
What happened to you?
It's nothing serious. Just a minor injury.
Let's go.
Tian Benchang.
Tian Bensheng.
You two...
I am Li Zhen,
paying respects to Lord He.
Your Excellency.
Li Zhen, you've suffered.
Li Zhen?
Why are you here?
Tian Benchang,
don't you get it yet?
I deliberately fell into your trap.
If not,
how could you walk right into my trap
and be caught with the contraband ink?
Ronghua, let's go separately.
I'll take the back door.
You go home quickly
so as not to arouse suspicion.
Go quickly.
Manager Zhen,
is there contraband ink
in the Tian family's dowry?
Mr. Xiao,
sorry to trouble you.
Escort Ronghua back later.
Make sure to keep an eye on
whether anyone is following her.
Was there anything unusual?
When Ronghua
was investigating the contraband ink,
she was almost discovered
by Tian Benchang.
I'm a little worried.
Don't worry.
Leave this to me.
Okay.
I stayed hidden and followed Tian Ronghua
all the way.
Manager Zhen,
just as you expected.
Those two boys from the Tian family
were also tailing her.
I was worried about the safety
of  Ronghua,
so I waited in a quiet place
outside for four hours.
Seeing nothing happen,
I finally dared to come back.
It seems
Tian Benchang already knows our plan.
But that doesn't make sense.
If he knew everything,
why wouldn't he take action?
If he wants that post
in the Directorate of Imperial Household,
he must move the ink quickly
and turn it into silver.
Yet he's sitting tight now.
He's clearly trying to mislead us.
The ink shouldn't be in the dowry anymore.
Tomorrow, during the bridal escort,
he will surely come up with another trick
to move the ink out.
Cuiqiao,
Mr. Xiao,
tomorrow, I still have
to follow the original plan
and get into the bridal sedan for Ronghua.
No, that's too risky.
No matter what Tian Benchang is thinking,
he must have a backup plan against you.
If you go so rashly,
won't you fall into his trap?
But if I don't go,
Tian Benchang
will be even more suspicious.
Only by falling into his trap
can I dispel his suspicion.
Not only me,
buttomorrow you and Doggie
must also stop the sedan chair as planned.
No.
It's still too dangerous.
If Master were here,
he wouldn't let you risk—
This is my only chance.
Only by doing so
will Wenqian have a chance of survival.
And only then can
Ronghua
and the Li family survive this.
I have no other choice.
Cuiqiao,
I can only take this risk.
Zhen.
Elders,
thank you for being
willing to help Li Ink.
Please accept my bow.
This...
Zhen.
The Tian family is steeped in evil.
With the Li family
suffering such a disaster,
how could we stand idly by?
Third Master is right.
If the Tian family is not rooted out,
it will ruin the entire
Huizhou ink industry.
We can't tolerate it any longer.
Zhen, Madam Wang has
already told us the whole story.
Just tell us
whatever you're planning.
Elders,
tomorrow I must find a way
to draw out Tian Benchang
and that batch of ink.
As for Cuiqiao and my grandfather,
they will surely
be watched by the Tian family,
making it hard for them to act.
After I enter the Tian Residence tomorrow,
the rest of the matters
will be left to you all.
Zhen, just say it.
We are all waiting for you
to make the plan
and assign the tasks.
First,
tomorrow's wedding procession
must be closely followed
to protect Ronghua's safety.
Secondly,
send someone to inform Prefect He
in advance.
Make sure he catches
them red-handed himself.
Third Grandfather.
President Hu.
I'm afraid
only you two can step forward for this.
Rest assured.
Don't worry, Zhen.
We represent
the Huizhou Literary Association.
If we go in person,
Prefect He should grant us an audience.
Third,
and most importantly,
tomorrow,
when Tian Benchang lets his guard down
and goes out to deliver the ink,
someone must closely follow him.
We must catch him red-handed.
I'm counting on you all.
It's me.
Zhen, I was worried about you.
Ronghua, listen to me.
Tian Benchang has known our plan.
What?
But don't worry.
Everything will go as originally planned.
Rest assured,
I've already arranged for someone
to protect you in secret.
So don't be afraid.
Keep this courtyard under strict watch.
Don't let anyone in or out as they please.
Go behind the screen! Hurry, this way.
Remember.
Stick to the original plan.
Your Excellency.
It's absolutely true.
I am willing to guarantee it
with the century-old reputation
of the Huizhou Literary Association.
Your Excellency, please come in person
and bring the Tian family
to justice in one stroke.
Your Excellency.
I just received word
while on patrol.
But I had the box opened
and inspected on the spot.
There was no contraband ink inside.
That's because Tian Benchang
changed the ink transportation route.
Your Excellency.
If the Literary Association
is not enough,
I am willing to stake the Chen Ink name
and my own life as guarantee.
Please dispatch troops!
Guards!
Your Excellency.
Assemble the constables.
Follow me to catch the criminals
with the loot.
And send a few men to the Tian family
to rescue Li Zhen.
Yes, Your Excellency.
Your Excellency.
Manager Zhen!
What are you doing?
We are looking for Manager Zhen.
Get out of the way!
Search!
Manager Zhen!
Your Excellency.
I, Li Zhen,
formally accuse the Tian family
of illicit foreign trade
through ink.
Under the guise
of marrying off his sister,
the Manager of the Tian Family,
Tian Benchang, concealed
contraband ink among the dowry chests
and later moved it here.
Please investigate thoroughly,
Your Excellency!
Your Excellency,
I saw with my own eyes
that nearly a thousand sticks
of Ziji Dragon Light Ink
specially made for illicit foreign trade
were hidden in my dowry.
Today, in order
to transport the ink, Tian Benchang
imprisoned innocent Li Zhen
and forced me to marry.
Please investigate thoroughly,
Your Excellency!
Your Excellency,
I, Chen Junshan, can also testify.
Moments ago,
Tian Benchang and Tian Bensheng
tried to flee
with this cart of contraband ink.
Having failed,
they were cornered here by us.
Please investigate thoroughly,
Your Excellency!
Guards,
search for the ink.
Found it, Your Excellency.
It really is contraband ink.
Arrest them!
Your Excellency,
the crimes committed by the Tian family
are not limited to this one.
Three years ago,
to seize the Luo family's property,
Tian Huai'an and Tian Benchang
colluded with County Magistrate Zhao She
and mercilessly
burned the entire Luo household alive.
The ink recipe
for this Ziji Dragon Light Ink
was stolen
from the Luo family's Young Master,
Luo Wensong.
Besides this,
since the Tian family
entered the ink industry,
they have been committing evil deeds,
repeatedly sabotaging other families.
My Li family alone
has suffered repeated schemes
at the Tian family's hands—
forced requisition of pine timber,
false accusations of illicit trade,
and other schemes.
Your Excellency, I also have a grievance
to voice.
When the mines were in chaos,
the Tian family recklessly annexed
ink workshops
and forced my father to his death.
They treat human lives as trifles,
utterly devoid of conscience.
Heaven itself would not
tolerate such evil.
Please investigate, Your Excellency.
Your Excellency,
I am willing to present evidence
of my own crimes.
During the previous Tribute Ink selection,
Sage Qing He's appraisal
was gravely unjust.
I hope Your Excellency
will report to the imperial court,
strip the Tian family of its status
as Tribute Ink supplier,
and return justice to the Chen Family.
Your Excellency.
Everything the ink industry members
said is true.
The Tian family
has committed numerous crimes.
Please uphold justice
for the Huizhou ink industry.
President Hu.
Your Excellency,
please uphold justice
for Huizhou's ink industry!
Everyone, quickly.
Please rise.
Regarding today's matter,
I
shall judge this matter
with strict impartiality!
Tian Benchang,
confess immediately!
Your Excellency, please understand.
I came across some documents
relating to illicit foreign trade
at home today by chance.
That's when I learned my second brother,
Tian Bensheng, was so audacious
as to conduct illicit foreign trade
through ink behind my back!
My brother was foolish,
and I was deeply grieved.
So I rushed here to stop him,
preventing him
from making further mistakes.
Your Excellency.
Benchang.
What kind of strategy is this?
What should I say?
Stop being stubborn!
Your Excellency.
Since he's handing
over the contraband ink,
he must have a deed with him
as proof of the transaction.
If you don't believe me,
just search him.
Benchang, what do you mean?
Bensheng!
Okay.
Search him!
Your Excellency, it's not like that.
This...
[Huizhou Prefecture Office]
Second Master.
Second Master,
please say something for me.
Wu Xin.
The Tian family is conducting
illicit foreign trade,
and were caught red-handed.
Aren't you going to tell the truth?
Who exactly
ordered you to frame the Li family?
I'll talk.
I will confess everything truthfully.
It was him.
He gave me ten taels of silver,
held my wife and children hostage,
and forced me to give false testimony
to frame the Li family.
Your Excellency.
I didn't dare to disobey, Your Excellency!
These were all Benchang's orders.
Tian Benchang gave the orders!
I just...
Your Excellency!
Your Excellency.
Since the Tian family
won the tribute ink contract,
I have been focusing on the ink workshop.
After learning that Benchang
was conducting illicit foreign trade,
I knew I had failed in my oversight
and was extremely ashamed.
I failed the young lady of the Li family
and Li Ink.
Up to today,
he has committed such a terrible disaster.
No matter
how Your Excellency punishes him,
I will have no complaints!
Your Excellency.
All of Tian Benchang's excuses
are just shirking responsibility.
Today, he fled with the ink,
and everyone saw it.
Besides, the people who transported ink
for the Tian family are right here.
Your Excellency,
you will know once you ask!
Move.
Your Excellency.
As per your orders,
we searched along the route
taken by Tian Benchang and Tian Bensheng.
At Baling Pavilion in the suburbs,
we found these three
were behaving suspiciously.
Upon investigation,
these three are the accomplices
receiving the contraband ink.
The three of you, confess at once.
Who was the one colluding with you
to traffic ink
through illicit foreign trade?
The one who contacted us
was Tian Bensheng.
Nonsense!
You're talking nonsense!
He's talking nonsense!
How dare you!
You dare lie
before Lord He?
Your Excellency heard it.
He has already testified
that this matter has nothing
to do with me.
Just now, Li Zhen
said I fled with the ink.
I must clarify this matter.
After I discovered Bensheng
was conducting illicit foreign trade,
I immediately went to stop him.
But he...
But he intended to flee.
I had no choice
but to chase him all the way.
This led to a misunderstanding
among the ink merchants, Your Excellency.
Tian Benchang!
Are you even human?
You are lying!
Tian Benchang,
you are clearly the mastermind
behind the illicit foreign trade!
Bensheng!
Those documents
all bear your seal and signature.
How long will you keep denying it?
You forced my hand to stamp them!
You forced...
Bensheng!
Having reached this point today,
you should come to your senses, Bensheng.
Don't say I'm the mastermind, Benchang.
Don't say it was me.
I beg you.
-Why did you say I was the mastermind?
-Your Excellency!
Tian Bensheng is dull and incompetent.
Everyone in Huizhou knows this.
No one would believe
that he could have concealed
his involvement
in illicit foreign trade
from the entire Tian family.
Besides,
all affairs of the Tian family
are entirely
under Tian Benchang's control.
If the illicit foreign trade
was done by Tian Bensheng alone,
how could Tian Benchang,
the manager of the Tian family,
remain unaware of it?
Your Excellency,
I can also testify.
Bensheng always
follows Benchang's lead.
Regarding the illicit foreign trade,
even if Bensheng handled it,
the mastermind behind it
must be Tian Benchang.
You useless thing!
Do you want all the Tian family to die
before you are satisfied?
Father!
The mastermind of this matter
is clearly Benchang.
At this point,
why are you still covering for him?
I'll beat you to death,
you selfish and unfilial daughter!
Tian Huai'an,
you need to think clearly
about exactly who dragged your Tian family
into this situation.
Are you really going
to stand by and watch
your second son
die in place of your eldest?
Father. Father.
Say something for me.
Say something for me, Father.
Benchang forced me
to do all of it.
You know it, Father.
Tian Huai'an,
regarding the Tian family's
illicit foreign trade,
did you know about it or not?
For the illicit foreign trade,
Bensheng was the one
who showed his face
for the documents, hiring, and delivery.
Father.
The lifeblood of our Tian family
rests entirely on my shoulders.
If it really comes to a last resort,
we can only use Bensheng as a scapegoat.
That's the only way the Tian family
can survive this crisis.
Father.
Day and night,
I devoted myself to the ink workshop.
Every ledger I handled
is completely clean.
Father,
you have seen them yourself.
How could I have conducted
illicit foreign trade, Father?
Your Excellency,
I truly know nothing
about the illicit foreign trade,
nor did I know my second son, Bensheng,
was carrying that batch of ink.
Bensheng,
just tell them the truth.
His Excellency will take into account
that this is your first offense
and a moment of foolishness,
and may show leniency.
Father!
I am your son, too, Father!
Are you giving up on me?
Master.
Bensheng is our son, too.
You can't do this, Master.
Shut up!
You can't do this!
Your Excellency,
can't you see it yet?
It's obvious that Tian Huai'an
has conspired with Tian Benchang
to make Tian Bensheng take the fall!
Please investigate thoroughly,
Your Excellency!
Your Excellency,
if you still have doubts
about my innocence,
you can immediately write
to Nanjing Commander Wu, Wu Ru.
He can stand as my guarantor.
Commander Wu is a military officer,
not a judge.
What guarantee can he
possibly offer for you?
Tian Benchang,
don't forget
that the Tian family's
illicit foreign trade is now a fact.
Why would Commander Wu
bring trouble upon himself now?
Li Zhen is right.
Please investigate thoroughly,
Your Excellency!
Tian family, Li family, hear the verdict!